Carlos Valladarez

Web developer

 ${\tt Cuenca, Ecuador \cdot +593-995867551 \cdot carlos-avb@hotmail.com \cdot linkedin.com/in/carlos-avb } \underline{{\tt Portfolio} \cdot {\tt Github PROFILE}}$

Web Developer specialized in React and Next.js with skills in JavaScript, SQL and NoSQL databases, and knowledge in Java, Kotlin, Python. Currently studying Software Engineering.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Black Horse Software Company.SAS | Cuenca, Azuay, Ecuador Backend Developer

DECEMBER 2023 —

- Microservices development with Spring Boot and Kotlin
 - XML handling with jdom2
 - Using Kafka for asynchronous communication between services
 - Using Quartz to schedule processes
- Development of fullstack functionalities
 - JSF and Primefaces
 - React and Electron

Proyetic.SAS | Cuenca, Azuay, Ecuador FullStack Developer

SEPTEMBER 2022 — OCTOBER 2022

- Development of a payment gateway (FrontEnd and Backend) with Django and relational databases
- Development of plugins for Wordpress and Prestashop using PHP

Banco del Austro | Cuenca, Azuay, Ecuador Development and QA Engineer

May 2022 — October 2022

- velopment and QA Engineer
 - Verification of the operation of various applications and migration status of them to new technologies
- Mobile applications testing

Kodeliv - SAS | Cuenca, Azuay, Ecuador

OCTOBER 2020 - APRIL 2022

Tech Lead

• Development of web applications using React, html, css, sass, and Firebase

Superintendency of Territorial Planning, Use and Land Management August 2019 — September 2019 Web Developer

• Development of a web application for user and file management for the Decentralized Autonomous Governments (GAD's), using javascript, bootstrap, and MongoDB

EDUCATION

Software Engineering | Cuenca, Ecuador

PRESENT

Universidad Católica de Cuenca

SKILLS

Programming: React, Next.js, JavaScript, HTML & CSS, SQL, NoSQL, Java, Python, PHP

Language skills: English: Intermediate proficiency Spanish: Native speaker

COMMUNITY SERVICE

Microsoft Student UCuenca | Cuenca, Azuay, Ecuador

SEPTEMBER 2018 – JUNE 2019

Trainer

• The project aims to train and guide high school seniors of the Daniel Hermida Educational Unit in the technological field through workshops and training